# ADAM T'KOY

https://www.linkedin.com/in/adam-tkoy/ https://github.com/AdamTKoy a.p.tkoy@gmail.com | 630-363-0924

With a strong foundation in computer science, I quickly adjust to new programming languages and problem solving challenges. I push myself to achieve worthy goals and always try to turn work into fun. Most of all, I love to collaborate because working with amazing people has been the highlight of all my prior experiences.

#### **SKILLS**

- Proficient in C, C++, Java, Python, and R using IDEs like Visual Studio, R-Studio and Xcode
- Led as front-end developer for semester-long group project creating web app with React, Node.js
- · Completed additional learning outside degree in Javascript, Python Pandas, Ruby, SQL, Swift
- Experience with version control using GitHub
- Experience coding in a Linux environment

### **EDUCATION**

# University of Illinois at Urbana-Champaign

GPA: 3.91/4.00

August 2024

Bachelor of Science in Statistics and Computer Science

Relevant coursework includes: Computer Architecture, Programming Languages & Compilers, Software Design Lab, Statistics Programming Methods, System Programming

#### **EXPERIENCE**

Genius Admin Naperville, IL

Apple Store

March 2022 - August 2023

- Efficiently resolved repair issues
- · Managed and tracked progress of repairs both in-store and at offsite repair facility
- Collaborated across store teams to ensure excellent customer experiences
- Received a merit bonus 3 times for performance and dedication

## Career Experience

Cupertino, CA

Apple

January 2023 - June 2023

Supported the Manufacturing Quality Engineering, Color team for 5 months, full-time:

- Operated special equipment to measure samples for color and texture
- Cleaned and manipulated data in Tableau to generate summary reports and visualizations
- Coordinated parts during sample reviews with Industrial Design team
- Sorted, labeled and stored part samples for long-term archival project

## **Product Specialist**

Naperville, IL

Apple Store

November 2019 - March 2022

• Efficiently created solutions for customers, including sales support, data migration and initial setup, and basic troubleshooting

## **Program Support Specialist**

Glen Ellyn, IL

College of DuPage

December 2017 - November 2019

- Analyzed student data to create and update statistical reports each semester
- Updated 3 internal data resource websites using HTML